Hello? Didn't you hear me knock?
怎么了? 你没听见我敲门吗?
Hi Mom. I'm sorry.
你好妈妈. 对不起.
I'm a little preoccupied.
我心里正想事儿呢.
What's wrong?
有什么事儿吗?
I can't find my keys.
我的钥匙找不到了.
I'm always losing them.
我老是把钥匙弄丢.
Do you remember what I did when you were little?
你还记得你小时候我是怎么做的吗?
What?
怎么做的?
In the winter,
在冬天,
you were always losing your gloves.
你老是弄丢手套.
And so I would attach them to your sleeves with little clips.
所以我就用小别针把它们别在你的袖子上.
It generally worked,
这个办法通常很管用,
although sometimes you still managed to lose them.
但是有时候你还是有本事把它们弄丢.
Don't ask me how.
别问我是怎么丢的.
I wish I could clip my keys to my sleeves.
但愿我能把钥匙别在袖子上.
Maybe you're pregnant.
也许你怀孕了.
Mother.
妈妈.
I was always very absent-minded when I was pregnant.
我怀孕时老是心不在焉.
I was not absent-minded.
我倒没有心不在焉.
I constantly craved cheeseburgers.
只是老想吃奶酪汉堡.
That's right.
一点儿不错.
Cheeseburgers? Hi Grammy.
奶酪汉堡? Hi外婆.
I didn't know you were here today.
我不知道您今天会来.
Well, I usually get my hair done on Wednesdays.
Well, 我通常星期三做头发.
But my stylist is on vacation this week,
但是我的发型师这周休假,
so I decided to visit.
所以我决定来看你们.
Come here, sweetheart. How are you?
过来, 宝贝. 你好吗?
Good.
很好.
Have you decided what you want to do for your birthday?
你决定好怎么过生日了吗?
We're having a party here,
我们要在这儿开晚会,
then I'm going out with my friends.
然后我和朋友们一起出去.
That sounds terrific.
太棒了.
Yeah.
是啊.
So are you staying for dinner?
您留下来吃晚饭是吗?
Why don't you?
为什么不呀?
We're planning to get take-out,
我们打算去买些快餐,
if I can ever find my...
如果我能找到我的...
Mom, why are your keys in the fruit bowl?
妈妈, 你的钥匙怎么在水果盘里?